Finding Aid for the The Papers of Edmund M. Morgan, Jr. (1878-1966)
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series VII -- Collected Writings
  - Frankfurter, Felix. "Distribution of Judicial Power Between the Courts of the United States and the Courts of the States," New Jersey Bar Association, 2 June 1928 (Box 15)
  - ------------------. Remarks at the dinner of the American Law Institute on the occasion of Judge (Box 15)
  - Learned Hand's retirement, Washington, D.C., 18 May 1951 (Box 15)
  - Freund, Paul A. "The Supreme Court Crisis," Brandeis University, 12 November 1958 (Box 15)
  - Speeches and Addresses (cont'd) (Box 15)
  - Hanify, Edward B. Address. (date and occasion unknown) (Box 15)
  - Howland, Prof. Address at Yale University on Armistice Day, 11 November 1932. (Box 15)
  - Landis, Dean?. "Pre-Legal Education," nd. (Box 15)
  - Sims, Cecil. "The Lawyer and the Classics," address before the annual meeting of the Arkansas Bar Association, Hot Springs, 13 May 1954 (Box 15)
  - Steele, Thomas M. "Why All the Fuss?" (excerpt), c. 1930. (Box 15)
  - Weinstein, Jack. "Some Thoughts on Legislation, Alcohol, and Drivers in the United States," address delivered at the Second International Conference on Alcohol and Road Traffic, Toronto, 12 September 1953. (Box 15)
  - Wyzanski, Charles E., Jr. "Constitutionalism -- Limitations and Affirmation," remarks at Marshall Conference, 24 September 1955 (Box 15)